

Satya Mandavalli

Nationality: Indian | Gender: Male | Phone number: (+48) 729651152 (Mobile)

Email address: satya.mandavalli@gmail.com LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/satya-mandavalli-a9398919

Skype: murthymnv@outlook.com | **Whatsapp Messenger:** +48729651152 |

Address: Łakowa 16, 31-443 Kraków, 31-443, Krakow, Poland (Home)

About me:

18 years of experience in cloud and VDI technologies like Azure IaaS, Azure AVD, Citrix Cloud, VMware, and Microsoft Windows Server AD Support. Extensive project experience, "from RFP to BAU support handover." IT infrastructure project implementation (technical), client coordination, Resource Management, and planning experience using MS Visio and Project tools. As an architect and implementation consultant, I have extensive experience with transition and transformation projects. Good technical document writing experience in HLD, LLD, and SOP. Good experience in the pre-sales experience as well. Being an Indian with a Blue Card (Karta Pobytu) working in Poland and looking for a good opportunity across EU countries.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/11/2021 - CURRENT Krakow, Poland

ENTERPRISE ARCHITECT CAPGEMINI POLAND

- France-based client: Citrix infra automation project: Worked as Citrix architect to automate Citrix VAD 1912 on-prem infra components automation through Ansible.
- Belgium-based telecom client: Citrix cloud Project, Worked as Citrix Architect for Citrix Cloud project to implement a greenfield environment.
- Germany-based group client: Citrix Architect migrated 400+ Citrix apps/servers into the cloud.
- Germany-based Pharma client: working as Azure architect. 10K+ Azure AVD implementation and other Azure-based projects.
- RFP, KT, Design, and Deployment

29/05/2019 - 11/10/2021 Hyderabad, India

SYSTEM ARCHITECT TECH MAHINDRA INDIA

- VMWare Horizon BAU project (Horizon 7.13/DEM/UAG/Instant clone VDI) 2000 Full and Instant Clone VDI Support.
- 10 members of VMWare Horizon L2 and L3 people management
- Citrix 6.5, 7.15 End to end support as L4 architect.
- Citrix NetScaler with GSLB on AWS Cloud Build and support.
- Citrix and VMWare Horizon Solution Designs
- Citrix Cloud with Azure Solution Designs ·
- \bullet Citrix's implementation and handover to BAU \cdot RFP, KT, Design, and Deployment \cdot Working as Architect for Citrix practice \cdot
- Working in multiple implementation projects •
- Participating in Pre Sales technical meetings · Project plan, Budget plan for Citrix implementation projects. · People management. ·
- Good PowerShell Knowledge with real-time experience in Citrix environments.

07/08/2017 - 30/12/2018 Hyderabad, India

MANAGER CAPGEMINI INDIA

- Anglian Water, UK Citrix XenApp XenDesktop 7.15 LTSR Solution Designs
- VMWare Horizon and Citrix Cloud with Azure Solution Designs
- VMWARE Horizon BAU support as an Architect.
- RFP, KT, Design, and Deployment

LEAD CONSULTANT WIPRO TECHNOLOGIES INDIA

- 13,000+ Wipro internal users VDI's Implemented
- Virtua Desk (Wipro Technologies Citrix cloud brand name) project
- Worked on multiple implementation projects like Royal DSM, Ingredion
- Multiple VMWare and Citrix XenApp training given to L1 and L2 resources in different Wipro Technologies branches
- Resource loading, Project plan, Budget plans for VMWARE and Citrix Transition and Transformation projects

09/11/2005 - 28/08/2014 Hyderabad, India

SYSTEM ENGINEER TO LEAD CONSULTANT CYIENT, IBM INDIA, SYNTEL, CSC INDIA LIMITED

- Worked as a Windows Server Support admin, VMWARE ESXi and Citrix SME
- Multiple projects and BAU support

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

23/10/2019 - 17/08/2022 India

MASTER OF ARTS Andhra University

Address Visakhapatnam, India, India

31/05/1996 - 28/02/1999 Vizag, India

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.SC) Andhra University

Address Vizag, India

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **TELUGU**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Azure Architecture | AZURE | Azure administration | Citrix Cloud management | Horizon View

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

ORGANISATIONAL SKILLS

Azure laaS, Azure AVD, Citrix Cloud, VMWare, and Microsoft Technologies Skills Fluent English

• Participates as an infrastructure Architect representative on Cloud Infra design; development; implementation, and/or integration of desktop virtualization environments.

Experience in

- Citrix VirtualApps and Desktop, Xenapp, XenDesktop
- VMware Horizon and Azure AVD VDI technologies Specialist
- Azure AVD environments
- · Citrix to AVD Migrations
- On-prem to Cloud (Azure) Migrations
- Citrix MetaFrame 4.5 to Latest Cloud
- Citrix NetScaler
- VMware Horizon VDI
- IT Infra and Cloud Solutions.
- RFI, RFP, Presales

- IT Architecture documentation (HLD, LLD, DD and SOPs)
- Project Management
- People Management
- Client Coordination
- Pre-Sales Architect
- Transitions and Transformation consultant

TECHNICAL CERTIFICATES

23/12/2022 - 22/12/2023

AZ-140

Configuring and Operating Microsoft Azure Virtual Desktop

AZ-500

AZ-300 & 301

AZ-400

1Y0-A20

2V0-01.19 VMware vSphere 6.7 Foundations Exam 2019

1Y0-200 Managing Citrix XenDesktop 7 Solutions

SKILLS & CAPABILITIES

Skills & Capabilities

Azure Virtual Desktop (AVD or WVD) - 2+ Years Experience Citrix Metaframe, XenApp, XenDesktop, Virtual Apps and Desktop, NetScaler - 10+ Years of Experience VMWARE Horizon - 3+ Years of Experience Windows Server & Active Directory - 15+ Years of Experience AppSense, AppLayer, PowerShell - Good Experience

SME, Consultant, Architect -- Technical positions People Management, Project Management, Pre Sales Architect

Looking for a Better salary. No "location/country" specific constraint within EU. Not interested on B2B or C2H Positions. One month notice period.